http://www.workamper.com/workamper-news-privacy-policy

Jump to Navigation
Workamper News
Mobile Menu
The Original Resource Of Jobs For RVers, Since 1987!
Search
WorkampingJoin Today!
Featured Employers
EmployingJoin Today!
Workamper News Privacy Policy
WORKAMPER NEWS PRIVACY POLICYYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by Workamper News Inc. and its subsidiaries.The Information We Collect
Through Workamper News Inc. publications, websites, and other media, you can order publications and products, engage in various activities like building a resume, creating a profile, marking your location on our member map, taking surveys, voting in polls, subscribing to our magazine, and participating in one of our online forums or communities. Your personally identifiable information may be required to engage in these activities as well as to receive products and services that you may have requested. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages and elsewhere include but are not limited to: name, address, gender, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number and credit or debit card information.
We may also collect information about your personal or professional interests and use of or opinions about various products, programs and services. Through certain promotions, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name, mailing and/or e-mail address, or member number with our Find-A-Reader promotion. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address and telephone number, or member number.We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our web pages or use our applications, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, your IP address, your device identifiers, your Internet or wireless service provider, and location-based information.How We Use the Information
We may use the information you provide about yourself or others to fulfill requests for our publications, products or services, to respond to inquiries about offerings and to offer other products, programs or services that may be of interest.We may combine information we receive with outside records and share such information with third parties for use on our behalf to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you.We may disclose personally identifiable information that we receive from you and from third party sources to third parties whose practices are not covered by this privacy statement (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you.When you request a magazine, service, or other product, we will forward the information you give us to the publisher or provider to the extent necessary to fulfill your request. They may contact you with special offers of possible interest.We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you, or to contact you about your account.If you choose to submit content (e.g., a "letter to our editors" or an online review), we may publish your name, screen name and other information you have provided to us. You hereby consent to this. The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our publications and websites, and to enable us to customize your Internet experience. We also may use this information to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.Agents and contractors of Workamper News Inc. that have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Workamper News Inc.We may transfer your personally identifiable information to other Workamper News Inc. offices for internal management and administrative purposes on our behalf. Your personal data will be transferred to other Workamper News Inc. offices where necessary for the performance or conclusion of our contractual obligations to you or for your benefit. To the extent not prohibited under applicable law, transfers and disclosures of personally identifiable information may also be made where necessary for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims, to protect the rights and property of Workamper News Inc., our agents, customers, and others, including to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of use; or to protect the personal safety of any person.
Please note that if Workamper News Inc. or any of its subsidiaries or lines of business is merged, acquired, divested, financed, sold, disposed of or dissolved, including through merger of, consolidation, sale or divestiture of assets, the relevant customer database, including personally identifiable information we may possess about you, may, in whole or in part, be sold, disposed of, transferred, divested, or otherwise disclosed as part of that transaction or proceeding.Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.Privacy OptionsIf you prefer not to receive e-mail marketing or other on-line promotions, or traditional mail or other off-line promotions from Workamper News Inc. you may opt-out of these types of promotions from the Manage Account page after logging into the website.Workamper News Inc. will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Workamper News Inc. also allows you to connect with other sites and services in order to share content and information.You should consult the other sites' and services' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties or their use of your information.Workamper News Inc. sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, editorial features, or other activities or offerings that are sponsored or co-sponsored by or presented with identified third parties. By virtue of your participation in such activities or offerings, your IP address and the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit may be provided to both the Workamper News Inc. site and the third parties. Workamper News Inc. has no control over the third parties' use of this information.Workamper News Inc. sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve advertisements, including online behavioral advertisements, that you may see on the web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements.This privacy notice does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you (e.g., type of browser, operating system, domain name, day and time of visit, page(s) visited) or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs).CookiesTo enhance your experience on our Services, we may place "cookies" on your computer or device. Cookies are small text files that we place in your computer or device to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering with one of our Services. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. A cookie assigns a unique numerical identifier to your Web browser or device, and may enable us to recognize you as the same user who has used our Services, and relate your use of the Services to other information about you, such as your usage information and personal information.We use cookies (and Local Shared Objects, HTML5, cache cookies, web beacons, or clear gifs, all described further below) to understand usage of the Services and to improve our content and offerings and to deliver advertisements that you might be interested in. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on our Services (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site, to save your password in password-protected areas, to enable shopping carts, or to tailor content or product and service offerings).
Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can set your browser option so that you will not receive cookies and you can also delete existing cookies from your browser. However, you may find that some parts of the site will not function properly if you have refused cookies or similar tracking technologies and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar tracking technologies might prevent you from accessing some of our content. However, your viewing of editorial content may be hampered. If you wish to block cookies, go to http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ to find out how, or check your browsers instructions.Local Shared Objects: Local shared objects, such as .Flash cookies,. also may be stored on your computer or device. Local shared objects operate a lot like cookies, but cannot be managed in the same way. Depending on how local shared objects are enabled on your computer or device, you may be able to manage them using software settings. For information on managing Flash cookies, for example, see http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flas....HTML 5: HTML5, the language some Web sites are coded in, may be used to store information on your computer or device about your Service usage activities. This information may be retrieved by us to help us manage our Services, such as by giving us information about how our Services are being used by our visitors, how they can be improved, and to customize them for our users.
Cache Cookies: Cache cookies, such as eTags, may be used to identify your computer or device as the same computer or device that visited a Service or Services in the past.
Web Beacons: Our websites may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. A web beacon is an electronic image called a single-pixel or clear GIF. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information, such as a user's cookie number, time and date of a page view, and description of the page where the web beacon is placed. These web beacons may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy above.These tracking technologies may be deployed by us and/or by our service providers or partners on our behalf. These technologies enable us to assign a unique number to you, and relate your Service usage information to other information about you, including your personal information. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both personal information and Service usage information, and use such information along with offline and online information obtained from other sources (including third parties) such as demographic information and updated contact information (where that information has been lawfully disclosed to us) for the purposes of learning more about you so we can provide you with relevant content.
Our Commitment to SecurityWe have put in place appropriate administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect. No system can be completely secure, however, and we do not guarantee that unauthorized disclosures and access will not happen.Accessing, Correcting, and Deleting Your Personal InformationWe will take reasonable steps to accurately record the personal information that you provide to us and any subsequent updates. We encourage you to review, update, and correct the personal information that we maintain about you, and you may request that we delete personal information about you that is inaccurate, incomplete, or irrelevant for legitimate purposes, or are being processed in a way which infringes any applicable legal requirements, by contacting us as set out in the "How to Contact Us" section below. At our election, instead of deleting such information, we may retain it with your comment or correction noted in our records. By contacting us, you may also object to our further use of your personal information if you have compelling legitimate grounds (this may involve closing your account). We may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information. Your right to review, update, correct, and delete your personal information may be limited, subject to the law or your jurisdiction: (i) if your requests are abusive or unreasonably excessive, (ii) where the rights or safety of another person or persons would be encroached upon, or (iii) if the information or material you request relates to existing or anticipated legal proceedings between you and us, or providing access to you would prejudice negotiations between us or an investigation of possible unlawful activity. Your right to review, update, correct and delete your information is subject to our records retention policies and applicable law, including any statutory retention requirements.
Retention of Personal InformationWe will retain your personal information while you have an account with us and thereafter for as long as we need it for purposes not prohibited by applicable laws. Thereafter, we will either delete your personal information or de-identify it so that it is anonymous and not attributed to your identity. Your rights to request that we delete your personal information are set forth in the "Accessing, Correcting, and Deleting Your Personal Information" section above.Changes to this Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy may be changed by Workamper News Inc. The revised Privacy Policy will be posted to this page so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.How to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns about the Workamper News Inc. Privacy Notice or its implementation please contact us via email at info@workamper.com or by writing to:Workamper News Customer ServiceAttention: Consumer Affairs110 Tulaka Blvd, Ste. CHeber Springs, AR 72543This Privacy Policy was revised Sep. 16, 2014.
News
200th Issue Features Solos & USACE
October 26, 2020
Read the Nov/Dec issue of Workamper... Read more
More Stories
Media Library
Making a First Impression as a Workamper
Making a First Impression as a Workamper
We are absolutely blown away with the success that we have attained via... Read more
More Testimonials
WorkampingJoin Today!
EmployingJoin Today!
©1987-2020 Workamper News Inc.
Workamper®, Workamper® News, and Workamper.com®
are registered trademarks of Workamper News.
Workamper News Inc.
Celebrating over 25 years of helping great people find great jobs in great places
